Guide to the Warwick House Records, 1968-1978
University Archives Duke University Durham, N.C., USA
Warwick House records 1968-1978
University Archives, Duke University
Duke University. Warwick House.
0.2 Linear Feet 250 Items
Warwick House was home to undergraduate male students from around 1968 to 1978.
Contains the records of Warwick House, a non-selective residence hall for undergraduate men at Duke University. Types of material included are financial summaries, notes, and a small amount of correspondence. Major subjects include student life at Duke University, living groups, and male students. Materials date from 1968 to 1978.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
In off-site storage; 48 hours advance notice is required for use.
Provenance
The Warwick House Records were received by the University Archives as a transfer in 1980.
Historical Note
Warwick House was a non-selective living group for undergraduate men on Duke University's West Campus. The house contained a total of 30 rooms and was part of the Few Federation during the late 1970s. The Few Federation was a unifying group of several men's and women's independent houses and men's selective upperclass houses. As an independent living group, Warwick House was at times governed by the Association of Independent Houses, Office of Student Affairs, and the Office of Housing Management.
Collection Overview
Contains minutes, financial summaries, damage reports, appeals forms, and small amount of correspondence pertaining to the residents of Warwick House at Duke University from 1968 to 1978.
Subject Headings
These are searchable subject entries for this collection. Performing a search on these subjects in the Duke University Libraries online catalog will bring up other related research materials.
Duke University -- History
Duke University -- Students
Dormitories -- North Carolina
Residence and education
Student housing -- North Carolina -- Durham
Male college students
Related Material
Alspaugh House Records
Duke University Archives
Arts and Sciences Council Records, Item: Arts and Sciences Council. Residential Life Committee. Report, 1994
Duke University Archives
Association of Independent Houses Records
Duke University Archives
Baldwin Federation Records
Duke University Archives
Bassett House Records
Duke University Archives
Brown House Records
Duke University Archives
Few Federation Records
Duke University Archives
Gilbert-Addoms Residence Hall Records
Duke University Archives
Giles House Records
Duke University Archives
Jarvis House Records
Duke University Archives
Mirecourt House Records
Duke University Archives
Pegram House Records
Duke University Archives
S.H.A.R.E. Records
Duke University Archives
York House Records
Duke University Archives
Contents of Collection
- Container List
  - ASDU bookkeeping materials, ca. 1971 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Financial summaries and damage reports, 1968-1969 (Folder 2)
  - Financial summaries and damage reports, 1969-1970 (Folder 3)
  - Financial summaries and damage reports, 1970-1971 (Folder 4)
  - Financial summaries and damage reports, 1971-1972 (Folder 5)
  - Financial summaries and damage reports, 1972-1973 (Folder 6)
  - Financial summaries and damage reports, 1973-1974 (Folder 7)
  - Financial summaries and damage reports, 1974-1975 (Folder 8)
  - Financial summaries and damage reports, 1975-1976 (Folder 9)
  - Financial summaries and damage reports, 1977-1978 (Folder 10)